Guide to the Western Film Lobby Card and Poster Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Riding Shotgun, pressbook, folio, 8 pp., 1956 (Box 3)
  An Andre deToth western with Randolph Scott. In recent years, critics have belatedly discovered deToth's films, including this one.
- The Riding Tornado, lobby cards, 1932 (Box 3)
- Rim of the Canyon, lobby card, 1949 (Box 3)
- River's Edge, poster, 1957 (Box 3)
  Another important late western from director Allan Dwan.
- La Riviere Rouge (Red River), Belgian poster, 1948 (Box 3)
- Le Roi et Quatre Reines (The King and Four Queens), French pressbook, 4to, 4 pp., 1956 (Box 3)
  Raoul Walsh western with Clark Gable.
- Rootin' Tootin' Rhythm, lobby card, 1937 (Box 3)
  Early Gene Autry Republic western.
- Roy Rogers, Official Warner Brothers still with printed text affixed, 1945 (Box 3)
- Ruggles of Red Gap, photograph (8" x 10"), keybook still, double weight, with text on verso, 1935 (Box 3)
  Classic Leo McCarey western comedy.
- Saddle Tramp, pressbook, folio, 8 pp., 1950 (Box 5)
  Joel McCrea Universal western.
- Saga of Death Valley, lobby card, 1939 (Box 3)
- Saginaw Trail, poster, 1953 (Box 3)
- Saginaw Trail, lobby cards, 1953 (Box 3)
- San Francisco, promotional flyer, 12mo, 4 pp., 1936 (Box 3)
  MGM's epic about the San Francisco earthquake.
- Santa Fe, pressbook, folio, 12 pp., 1951 (Box 5)
  Randolph Scott western produced by Harry Joe Brown---early in a series of films where Brown would soon bring in Budd Boetticher to direct. This was the first collaboration of Scott with Brown.
- The Searchers, color stills, 1956 (Box 3)
  John Wayne in John Ford Western.
- Secret of Convict Lake, pressbook, small folio, 12 pp., 1951 (Box 3)
- Seven Cities of Gold, lobby card, 1955 (Box 3)
- Shaft, lobby cards (set of 8), 1971 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  Gordon Parks directed film, starring Richard Roundtree.
- Shane, photograph (8" x 10"), 1953 (Box 19)
  Alan Ladd film, directed by George Stevens.
- The Sherriff of Sage Valley, pressbook, folio, 8 pp., 1942 (Box 5)
  A PRC western featuring Buster Crabbe as Billy the Kid, this was one of a series of films in which he played this character.
- She's a Lone Wolf, 1936 (Box 3)
- Showdown, poster, 1950 (Box 3)
- Showdown at Boothill, poster, 1958 (Box 3)
- Silver Canyon, lobby card, 1951 (Box 3)
- Silver Stallion, poster, 1941 (Box 3)
- Singin' in the Corn, title lobby card, 1946 (Box 3)
- Sioux City Sue, lobby card, 1946 (Box 3)
- Soft Boiled, lobby card, 1923 (Box 3)
  Silent Tom Mix western.
- Son of Paleface, poster, 1952 (Box 3)
  Classic western comedy by Frank Tashlin, then early in his directing career, who was a favorite director of the French New Wave.
- The Son of the Golden West, lobby card, 1928 (Box 4)
  Silent Tom Mix film.
- South of the Border, lobby card, 1939 (Box 4)
- Stagecoach, window card poster, paper backed and Promotional flyer, 12mo, 4 pp., 1939 (Box 4)
  Extremely rare original poster for legendary John Ford film, in which he returned, after many years, to the western and, in some sense, reinvented it, and, in the process, made a genuine star of John Wayne.
  Promotional flyer contains a map of the route followed by the stagecoach as well as portraits of some of the film's main stars.
- Stagecoach, 1939 (Box 5)
- Stagecoach Buckaroo, poster, 1942 (Box 4)
- Stallion Road, photographs (8" x 10"), 1947 (Box 4)
  Reagan played a horse doctor in rural southern California, in one of his favorite films.
- Story of Will Rogers, lobby card, 1952 (Box 4)
- Sunset Pass, poster, 1946 (Box 4)
- Susanna Pass, lobby cards, 1949 (Box 4)
- Swamp Fire, lobby card, 1946 (Box 4)
- T-Men, pressbook (17" x 11"), 1948 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  Film noir, set in Southern California.
- Taking a Chance, lobby card, 1929 (Box 4)
  Silent Rex Bell western.
- Tennessee's Partner, photographs (8" x 10"), 1955 (Box 4)
  Classic Allan Dwan western adapted from story by Bret Harte. Dwan's career spanned all the way back to working with D.W. Griffith in the teens. He made many important films in the 20's and 30's, but, by the 50's, he was a forgotten man, and he actually made many of the films which critics rate most highly in those years, on low budgets, such as this one.
- Tennessee's Partner, lobby card, 1955 (Box 4)
- Terror of Bar X, lobby cards, 1927 (Box 4)
  Bob Custer silent western, this card has unusually bright hand coloring and vivid border art design.
- They Came to Cordura, photograph (8" x 10"), 1959 (Box 4)
  Robert Rossen film set in the Mexican desert during World War I.
- They Came to Cordura, title lobby card, 1959 (Box 4)
- They Died With Their Boots On, lobby card, 1941 (Box 4)
  Raoul Walsh film about Custer and Little Big Horn. This is a particularly interesting image of the Native Americans on the warpath.
- Those Redheads from Seattle, lobby cards, 1953 (Box 4)
  3-D western musical romance.
- Three Faces West, photograph (8" x 10"), 1940 (Box 4)
  John Wayne film set in North Dakota and Oregon, which traces some of the same themes as The Grapes of Wrath, which was released in the same year.
- A Ticket to Tomahawk, lobby card (11" x 14"), 1950 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  Marilyn Monroe western.
- Tortilla Flat, photographs (8" x 10"), double weight, date stamped, with printed text on verso, 1942 (Box 4)
  Photographs by the Hollywood photographer Clarence S. Bull, with his stamps also on verso. John Steinbeck's books, most of them set in the West, were the sources for a number of important Hollywood films, including this one.
- Tracked by the Police, lobby card, 1927 (Box 4)
  Rin Tin Tin drama set in Arizona. In the silent era, dog star Rin Tin Tin captured the imagination of movie audiences with dramas, most of which, like this one, were set in western locales.
- Trailin', lobby card, 1921 (Box 4)
  Tom Mix silent film.
- The Traveling Saleswoman, title lobby card, 1949 (Box 4)
- Trigger Happy, poster, 1963 (Box 4)
- Trouble in Texas, lobby card, 1937 (Box 4)
  Grand National film starring Tex Ritter and a very young Rita Hayworth, who was still being billed as Rita Cansino. An iconic closeup of cowboy Ritter and Hayworth.
- Tucson, Title lobby card, 1948 (Box 4)
- Two Gun Law, lobby cards, 1937 (Box 4)
  Charles Starrett western.
- Unconquered, photograph (8" x 10"), 1947 (Box 4)
  Cecil B. DeMille film.
- Unconquered Bandit, lobby cards, 1935 (Box 4)
  Tom Tyler western.
- Under California Stars, lobby card, 1948 (Box 4)
- Union Pacific, mini-window card poster, 1939 (Box 4)
  This was the smallest size of poster made in the 1930's, for Cecil B. DeMille western epic.
- Valley of Fire, lobby cards, 1951 (Box 4)
- Valley of Fire, 1951 (Box 4)
- Valley of Wanted Men, lobby cards, 1935 (Box 4)
- Vertigo, reissue lobby card (11" x 14"), 1963 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  1958 film, directed by Alfred Hitchcock, and starring James Stewart and Kim Novak.
- Virginia City (La Caravane Heroique), French poster on linen (Box 6 (Roll))
  Michael Curtiz directed Errol Flynn, Randolph Scott, Humphrey Bogart, and others in this epic western, done just at the cusp of Bogart's stardom.
- Virginia City (1956 reissue), poster, 1940 (Box 4)
- Virginia City, lobby card, from original release, on a linen-stock paper, 1940 (Box 4)
- Wanderer of the Wasteland, lobby cards, 1935 (Box 4)
  Adapted from Zane Grey novel.
- The Wayward Bus, lobby card from Steinbeck adaptation, 1957 (Box 4)
- The Westerner, lobby card (11" x 14"), 1940 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  William Wyler film.
- White Eagle, lobby card, circa 1932-1941 (Box 4)
  Early talking film with Buck Jones.
- Whoopee, promotional flyer, 12mo, 4 pp., 1930 (Box 4)
  Early talking western musical comedy.
- Wide Open Town, lobby card, 1941 (Box 4)
- The Wild Bunch, poster, 1969 (Box 18 (Broadside))
- The Wild Bunch, stationary, 1969 (Box 19)
- Wild Horse Canyon, lobby card, 1939 (Box 4)
  Jack Randall Monogram film.
- Wild Horse Valley, lobby cards, 1940 (Box 4)
- Die Wilden Von Sunset Strip (Riot on Sunset Strip), German poster on linen (Box 12 (Roll))
  An example of a film with a 60's theme, the artwork is telling about the continuing influence of California culture.
- Wolf Law, lobby card for silent Universal western, 1922 (Box 4)
- Young Jesse James, poster, 1960 (Box 4)